teachwithmovies.org 2019-06-19

# PRIVACY POLICY – TEACH WITH MOVIES

TeachWithMovies.org, Inc. (hereinafter “TWM”) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of its Users.

TWM does not obtain electronic financial information from Users. When Users donate money to TWM through a credit or debit card, the donation will be made through a third-party such as PayPal which has sophisticated anti-hacking programs. Users will have to check the privacy policies of such organizations. If Users donate using a check sent to TWM, TWM will not provide any banking information about the User to any other person or entity except to deposit the check in TWM’s bank and except as may be required by any governmental agency or court. Usage data, the TWM User’s name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address will not be sold, leased, rented or provided in any manner to any person or organization, except to make authorized charges against the TWM User’s credit card or PayPal account.

**Cookies**

Third Party Vendors, including without limitation, Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our site. Google’s use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. We use Google AdSense on our site. Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

**[https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en](https://support.google.com/adspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en&visit_id=636779270040665371-3235021539&rd=1)**

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick DART cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [**Ads Settings**](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [**aboutads.info**](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

**Google Analytics**

We use “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit, when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site.

Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google.

Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [**Google Analytics Terms of Use**](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/) and the [**Google Privacy Policy**](https://policies.google.com/privacy). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [**disabling cookies**](https://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions) on your browser. For more information on Google Analytics, please visit **[Google Analytics](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/).**

**Third Parties**

TWM is not aware of the privacy policies of any third party and has no control over any third party to which a link may be provided through TeachWithMovies.org or TeachWithMovies.com, including without limitation, Amazon.com.

**Children**

TeachWithMovies.com is designed for educators, parents, and other adults concerned with the education of children. It is not designed for use by K-12 students or any person under the age of 18.

**Security**

TWM is not responsible for any breach of its security or for the actions of any third parties that may wrongfully or unlawfully obtain any personal information about TeachWithMovies.com Users. TWM does not have the technical sophistication to protect personal information from hackers. TWM will not knowingly provide personal information about any TWM User.

**Exception for Subpoenas and Orders from Governmental Organizations**

This privacy policy does not apply to any subpoena or any order from a court or administrative agency that requires TeachWithMovies.com, Inc. to disclose personal information about its Users.

**E-mail:**

Inquiries concerning our privacy policy should be addressed to James Frieden, Secretary/Treasurer of TeachWithMovies.com, Inc. as follows:

e-mail: support@TeachWithMovies.com  
Telephone: 310-917-1940  
Fax: Send a fax to (866) 653-0684

Mail: TeachWithMovies.com, Inc.  
1717 Fourth Street, Third Floor  
Santa Monica, CA 90401-3319

**Changes to Policy**

TWM reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying TeachWithMovies.com Users (through posting a notice at this location or by e-mail).
